import { HeroCardDefinition } from './HeroCard';

export const HERO_CARDS: HeroCardDefinition[] = [
  {
    "id": "1",
    "name": "Boomer Bot",
    "description": {
      "front": "Kill all ENEMY at a location. Burnout.",
      "back": "Kill all ENEMY at two locations. Burnout."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 1,
      "batteryCount": 0,
      "gearCount": 1
    },
    "activationNumber": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "name": "Defense Drone",
    "description": {
      "front": "Kill 1 ENEMY.",
      "back": "Kill 2 ENEMY."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 2,
      "batteryCount": 0,
      "gearCount": 2
    },
    "activationNumber": 3
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "name": "Sentry Unit",
    "description": {
      "front": "Kill 2 ENEMY.",
      "back": "Kill 3 ENEMY."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 3,
      "batteryCount": 0,
      "gearCount": 3
    },
    "activationNumber": 4
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "name": "Valor Victoria",
    "description": {
      "front": "Kill 3 ENEMY.",
      "back": "Kill 5 ENEMY."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 1,
      "dataCount": 4,
      "batteryCount": 0,
      "gearCount": 4
    },
    "activationNumber": 5
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "name": "Centurion",
    "description": {
      "front": "Kill 4 ENEMY.",
      "back": "Kill 6 ENEMY."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 2,
      "dataCount": 5,
      "batteryCount": 0,
      "gearCount": 5
    },
    "activationNumber": 6
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "name": "Basher Bot",
    "description": {
      "front": "Hack all LOCK at a location. Burnout.",
      "back": "Hack all LOCK at two locations. Burnout."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 1,
      "dataCount": 1,
      "batteryCount": 0,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "name": "Breach Drone",
    "description": {
      "front": "Hack 1 LOCK.",
      "back": "Hack 2 LOCK."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 2,
      "dataCount": 2,
      "batteryCount": 0,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 3
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "name": "Keyjack Unit",
    "description": {
      "front": "Hack 2 LOCK.",
      "back": "Hack 3 LOCK."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 3,
      "dataCount": 3,
      "batteryCount": 0,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 4
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "name": "Coding Clyde",
    "description": {
      "front": "Hack 3 LOCK.",
      "back": "Hack 5 LOCK."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 4,
      "dataCount": 4,
      "batteryCount": 1,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 5
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "name": "Infiltrator",
    "description": {
      "front": "Hack 4 LOCK.",
      "back": "Hack 6 LOCK."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 5,
      "dataCount": 5,
      "batteryCount": 2,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 6
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "name": "Extinguisher Bot",
    "description": {
      "front": "Clear all HAZARD at a location. Burnout.",
      "back": "Clear all HAZARD at two locations. Burnout."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 0,
      "batteryCount": 1,
      "gearCount": 1
    },
    "activationNumber": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "name": "Containment Drone",
    "description": {
      "front": "Clear 1 HAZARD.",
      "back": "Clear 2 HAZARD."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 0,
      "batteryCount": 2,
      "gearCount": 2
    },
    "activationNumber": 3
  },
  {
    "id": "13",
    "name": "Sanitation Unit",
    "description": {
      "front": "Clear 2 HAZARD.",
      "back": "Clear 3 HAZARD."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 0,
      "batteryCount": 3,
      "gearCount": 3
    },
    "activationNumber": 4
  },
  {
    "id": "14",
    "name": "Hazmat Hank",
    "description": {
      "front": "Clear 3 HAZARD.",
      "back": "Clear 5 HAZARD."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 1,
      "batteryCount": 4,
      "gearCount": 4
    },
    "activationNumber": 5
  },
  {
    "id": "15",
    "name": "Dozer",
    "description": {
      "front": "Clear 4 HAZARD.",
      "back": "Clear 6 HAZARD."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 2,
      "batteryCount": 5,
      "gearCount": 5
    },
    "activationNumber": 6
  },
  {
    "id": "16",
    "name": "Spotter Bot",
    "description": {
      "front": "Scout a location. Burnout.",
      "back": "Scout two locations. Burnout."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 1,
      "batteryCount": 1,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "17",
    "name": "Survey Drone",
    "description": {
      "front": "Scout a location in the **Outer Limits**.",
      "back": "Scout a location in **Lowline Commons** or closer."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 2,
      "batteryCount": 2,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 3
  },
  {
    "id": "18",
    "name": "Scanner Unit",
    "description": {
      "front": "Scout a location in **Lowline Commons** or closer.",
      "back": "Scout a location in **Silicon Heights** or closer."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 3,
      "batteryCount": 3,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 4
  },
  {
    "id": "19",
    "name": "Recon Riley",
    "description": {
      "front": "Scout a location in **Silicon Heights** or closer.",
      "back": "Scout a location in the **Blacklight District** or closer."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 4,
      "batteryCount": 4,
      "gearCount": 1
    },
    "activationNumber": 5
  },
  {
    "id": "20",
    "name": "Ranger",
    "description": {
      "front": "Scout a location.",
      "back": "Scout two locations."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 5,
      "batteryCount": 5,
      "gearCount": 2
    },
    "activationNumber": 6
  },
  {
    "id": "21",
    "name": "Scavenger Drone",
    "description": {
      "front": "Find 1 additional resource at a location.",
      "back": "Find 2 additional resources at a location."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 1,
      "dataCount": 0,
      "batteryCount": 0,
      "gearCount": 1
    },
    "activationNumber": 3
  },
  {
    "id": "22",
    "name": "Extraction Unit",
    "description": {
      "front": "Find 2 additional resources at a location.",
      "back": "Find 3 additional resources at a location."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 1,
      "dataCount": 1,
      "batteryCount": 1,
      "gearCount": 1
    },
    "activationNumber": 4
  },
  {
    "id": "23",
    "name": "Salvage Sam",
    "description": {
      "front": "Find 3 additional resources at a location.",
      "back": "Find 5 additional resources at a location."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 2,
      "dataCount": 2,
      "batteryCount": 2,
      "gearCount": 2
    },
    "activationNumber": 5
  },
  {
    "id": "24",
    "name": "Harvester",
    "description": {
      "front": "Find 4 additional resources at a location.",
      "back": "Find 6 additional resources at a location."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 3,
      "dataCount": 3,
      "batteryCount": 3,
      "gearCount": 3
    },
    "activationNumber": 6
  },
  {
    "id": "25",
    "name": "Overload Bot",
    "description": {
      "front": "Burnout another player's uncharged syn. Burnout.",
      "back": "Burnout another player's charged syn. Burnout."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 1,
      "batteryCount": 4,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "26",
    "name": "Reactor Unit",
    "description": {
      "front": "Charge an uncharged syn.",
      "back": "Charge a syn."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 0,
      "batteryCount": 5,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 4
  },
  {
    "id": "27",
    "name": "Robbie Recharge",
    "description": {
      "front": "Charge a syn.",
      "back": "Supercharge a syn."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 0,
      "batteryCount": 6,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 5
  },
  {
    "id": "28",
    "name": "Energizer",
    "description": {
      "front": "Supercharge a syn.",
      "back": "Charge two syns."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 0,
      "batteryCount": 7,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 6
  },
  {
    "id": "29",
    "name": "Junker",
    "description": {
      "front": "Conquer a location in the **Outer Limits**.",
      "back": "Conquer two locations in the **Outer Limits**."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 0,
      "batteryCount": 0,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 1
  },
  {
    "id": "30",
    "name": "Junker",
    "description": {
      "front": "Conquer a location in the **Outer Limits**.",
      "back": "Conquer two locations in the **Outer Limits**."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 0,
      "batteryCount": 0,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 1
  },
  {
    "id": "31",
    "name": "Junker",
    "description": {
      "front": "Conquer a location in the **Outer Limits**.",
      "back": "Conquer two locations in the **Outer Limits**."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 0,
      "batteryCount": 0,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 1
  },
  {
    "id": "32",
    "name": "Junker",
    "description": {
      "front": "Conquer a location in the **Outer Limits**.",
      "back": "Conquer two locations in the **Outer Limits**."
    },
    "resources": {
      "circuitCount": 0,
      "dataCount": 0,
      "batteryCount": 0,
      "gearCount": 0
    },
    "activationNumber": 1
  }
];
